var myFlashcards = [     {question:"anticipation requires arranged or combined in the same way as in the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">finisar and netmoneyin</span></a>'},{question:"if several meanings disclosure points to proper meanings of claim terms",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_30.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">renishaw</span></a>'},{question:"102 anticipation rejection can't pick and choose",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">netmoneyin&#44; arkley</span></a>'},{question:"for anticipation arranged as in the claim means not mere catalogues of separate parts",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_24.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">lindemann</span></a>'},{question:"for anticipation not enough that artisan might combine distinct teachings or parts to come up with invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_24.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"102(f)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">costello and facius</span></a>'},{question:"if ranges only slightly overlap no anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">innovatit and atofina</span></a>'},{question:"have to demonstrate criticality of range",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">ClearValue&#44; Atofina</span></a>'},{question:"ambiguous reference no good under 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_10.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">brink</span></a>'},{question:"for genus so large species not obviousness to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_26.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">wrigley</span></a>'},{question:"for incorporation by reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/de-seversky-strahilevitz-tap.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">De Seversky</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation is factual inquiry resolved by preponderance of the evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/epstein-ipxl-rishoi.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">epstein</span></a>'},{question:"determining that a claim is anticipated is a two step process",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/boyer-bush-celeritas-crish-kuhle.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">yorkey&#44; crish&#44; celeritas</span></a>'},{question:"inherency must be necesssarily present",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/demaco-rosco.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">rosco</span></a>'},{question:"can't import written description limitations into the claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/boston-scientific-flo-healthcare.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">flo healthcare</span></a>'},{question:"no picking&#44; choosing&#44; combining in a 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/arkley-boston-scientific.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">arkley</span></a>'},{question:"each and every limitation explicit or inherent for a 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/larson-ntp-jasinski-gulack.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">NTP&#44; Jasinski</span></a>'},{question:"silence in prior art doesn't meet 102 anticipation standard for disclosure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/robotic.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">robotic</span></a>'},{question:"examiner's factual findings about what reference discloses must be supported by preponderance of the evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/aslanian-baum-caveney.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">caveney</span></a>'},{question:"secondary considerations are not an element of anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/general-foods-cohesive-tech.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">cohesive tech</span></a>'},{question:"absence from reference of any claimed element negates anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/kloster-knorr-bremse.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">kloster&#44; knorr-bremse</span></a>'},{question:"Examiner erred finding prior art described embodiment in way enabling POSITA to make invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/09/clearvalue-therasence-sanofi-schreiber.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">clearvalue&#44; therasence&#44; sanofi&#44; schreiber&#44; spada&#44; bond</span></a>'},{question:"teaching away irrelevant to anticipation&#44; but disclosure is",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/10/seachange.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">seachange</span></a>'},{question:"if spec silent&#44; drawings not to scale can't be relied on as prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/10/mraz-hockerson-halberstadt.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">mraz&#44; hockerson-halberstadt</span></a>'},{question:"only if POSITA can at once envisage each member of a class does disclosure anticipate",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/10/petering.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">petering</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation cannot be predicated on ambiguous reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/11/turlay.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">turlay</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation requires lack of novelty&#44; all claim elements and limitations arranged as in the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/01/karsten.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">karsten</span></a>'},{question:"for 102 not enough that discloses part of claim which POSITA might supplement to make whole",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/01/perricone-net-moneyin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">perricone&#44; net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"inherent result must inevitably result from disclosed steps",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/03/montgomery.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">montgomery</span></a>'},{question:"absence from the reference of any claimed element negates anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/04/kloster.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">kloster</span></a>'},{question:"drawings can anticipate but must show POSITA all claimed features and how put together",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/05/mraz-jockmus-aslanian.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">mraz&#44; jockmus&#44; aslanian</span></a>'},{question:"Inherent anticipation requires more than presence of an unrecognized claimed de minimis quantity",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/07/nelson-crown-packaging.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">crown packaging</span></a>'},{question:"three separate means not anticipated by two means where one of two argued to meet two of three",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/07/lantech-robertson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">robertson</span></a>'},{question:"two snaps don't inherently anticipate disposable diapers requiring three snaps",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/07/playtex-robertson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">robertson</span></a>'},{question:"Inherency may not be established by probabilities or possibilities.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/07/therasence-schering-continental-can.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">therasense&#44; schering&#44; continental can</span></a>'},{question:"keystone of inherency is inevitability&#44; it can't be established by probabilities or possibilities",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/08/montgomery-mehl-halliburton-nautilus.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">montgomery&#44; MEHL</span></a>'},{question:"A claim is anticipated only if each element is found&#44; either express or inherent&#44; in a single prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/08/institut-pasteur.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">verdegaal</span></a>'},{question:"precise language of 102 places burden of proof on Patent Office",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/wilson-warner.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">warner</span></a>'},{question:"prior art must actually disclose invention&#44; not just be inherently capable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/perricone-minton-hoffer-griffin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">perricone</span></a>'},{question:"extrinsic evidence may be used to explain but not expand meaning of ref relied on for anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">baxter travenol</span></a>'},{question:"where reference is silent about asserted inherent characteristic&#44; must be necessarily present",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">continental can</span></a>'},{question:"absence of any claimed element negates anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">kloster</span></a>'},{question:"to anticipate prior art has to disclose every limitation either explicitly or inherently",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">schreiber</span></a>'},{question:"inherency cannot be established by probabilities or possibilities",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/schreiber-kloster-baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">therasense</span></a>'},{question:"no picking and choosing in anticipation rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/netmoneyin-arkley.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">Arkley</span></a>'},{question:"for anticipation all elements of the claim within four corners of the prior art ref arranged as in the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/netmoneyin-arkley.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">NetMoneyIN</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation each and every claim limitation explicitly or inherently",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/ntp-hansgirg-oelrich.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">NTP</span></a>'},{question:"no picking&#44; choosing&#44; and combining not directly related disclosures in 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/arkley.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">arkley</span></a>'},{question:"inherent anticipation doesn't require recognition in prior art&#44; and recourse to extrinsic evidence is proper",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/telemac-schering-digitech.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">telemac&#44; schering</span></a>'},{question:"extrinsic evidence ok to explain but not expand on meaning of ref in 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/baxter-travenol-netmoneyin-atmel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">baxter travenol</span></a>'},{question:"prima facie case not met when rejection so uninformative that applicant cannot counter the arguments",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/chester.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">chester</span></a>'},{question:"unless ref discloses within four corners not only all limitations but also arranged as in claim no 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/net-moneyin-hockerson-halberstadt-alza.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"a prior art ref anticipates a patent claim under 102(b) if it discloses every claim limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/montgomery-verizon.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">montgomery&#44; verizon</span></a>'},{question:"102 each and every limitation of claimed invention be disclosed in a single prior art reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/buszard-paulsen-tempo-lighting-zletz.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">buszard&#44; paulsen</span></a>'},{question:"disclosure of a genus in the prior art is not a disclosure of every species that is a member of that genus",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/atofina-lizardtech.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">atofina</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation needs all elements disclosed arranged as in the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/connell.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">connell</span></a>'},{question:"In order to anticipate identical invention must be shown in as complete detail as patent claim.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/jamesbury-connell.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">jamesbury&#44; connell</span></a>'},{question:"Unless reference discloses all limitations claimed&#44; arranged or combined in same way cannot anticipate",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/net-moneyin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"every claim limitation must identically appear in a single prior art reference for it to anticipate claim.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/gechter.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">gechter</span></a>'},{question:"102 prior art must not only disclose all elements of claim&#44; but also 'arranged as in the claim.'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/net-moneyin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"picking and choosing has no place in the making of a 102&#44; anticipation rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/arkley.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">arkley</span></a>'},{question:"To serve as an anticipating reference&#44; must enable that which it is asserted to anticipate",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/trading-tech-elan-pharm-donohue.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">elan pharm.&#44; donohue</span></a>'},{question:"for 102 every element expressly or inherently described in single prior art arranged as in claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/verdegaal-bond.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">verdegaal&#44; bond</span></a>'},{question:"Anticipation is a question of fact based on a preponderance of the evidence.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/baxter-travenol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">baxter travenol</span></a>'},{question:"finding merely functionally equivalent structure to anticipate the specific structure claimed was error",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/procter-gamble-grabiak-ruskin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">ruskin</span></a>'},{question:"prior art cannot anticipate if allegedly anticipatory disclosures cited as prior art are not enabled",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/antor-media.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">antor media</span></a>'},{question:"for 102 not enough that prior art includes multiple&#44; distinct teachings artisan might somehow combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/net-moneyin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">net moneyin</span></a>'},{question:"102 prior art must disclose each/every element of claimed invention arranged or combined in same way",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/blue-calypso-antares.html"><span style="color: #38761d;">blue calypso</span></a>'},{question:"remanded from Fed. Cir.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">stepan</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation word for word not necessary",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_20.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">standard havens</span></a>'},{question:"anticipatory reference need not be word for word",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_18.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">standard havens</span></a>'},{question:"prima facie burden met by adequately explaining shortcomings putting applicant on notice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1600.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">hyatt&#44; chester</span></a>'},{question:"efficacy inherent in method claims and merely proposed anticipates",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_22.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">montgomery</span></a>'},{question:"inherency in 2400 communications",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_21.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">transclean corp</span></a>'},{question:"rejection that has not been commented on by examiner is not adverse decision of board",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/bozek-mintz-perfect-web-paperless.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">paperless</span></a>'},{question:"discovery of unappreciated property does not render old composition new",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/atlas-powder-kollman-rinehart.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">atlas powder</span></a>'},{question:"Arguments must be commensurate in scope with the actual claim language.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/hiniker-self.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">self</span></a>'},{question:"prior art enablement only requires that it teach POSITA to make or carry out what it discloses",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/advanced-cardiovascular-antor-media.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">antor</span></a>'},{question:"intermediate products can anticipate",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/herbert-mullin.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">mullin&#44; herbert</span></a>'},{question:"claim construction centered on claim language",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-innova-miller-vogel.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">innova</span></a>'},{question:"diligence for constructive reduction to practice requires showing attorney diligence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/baldwin-interactive-gift-mulder-gould.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">bey</span></a>'},{question:"proof of due diligence required no matter how short the period&#44;",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/baldwin-interactive-gift-mulder-gould.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">mulder&#44; gould</span></a>'},{question:"prior art with each and every structural limitation capable of performing each and every function anticipates",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/ipxl-schreiber-ratti.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">schreiber</span></a>'},{question:"teaching away irrelevant to anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/biogen-seachange-depuy-spine.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">seachange</span></a>'},{question:"reduction to practice must show embodiment worked for its intended purpose but can be outside intended environment",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/jella-dsl-newkirk.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">dsl&#44; newkirk</span></a>'},{question:"need to provide evidence of criticality of claimed range",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/clearview.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">clearview</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation only requires suggestions in prior art be enabled",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/impax.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">Impax</span></a>'},{question:"burden of proof for inherency is on Examiner; burden of production met by adequately explaining shortcomings so applicant properly notified and able to respond; burden of proof shitfts to applicant to rebut prima facie finding of inherency",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/vitronics-best-crown-operations-jung.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">best&#44; crown operations; jung&#44; hyatt; best&#44; schreiber</span></a>'},{question:"in reexam burden of proof is preponderance of the evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/hyatt-fiers-morse-cls-swanson.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">swanson</span></a>'},{question:"even disparaged art can anticipate",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/09/celeritas.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">celeritas</span></a>'},{question:"disclosure of genus may anticipate species even if species not recited",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/12/petering-bristol-myers.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">petering&#44; bristol-myers</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation: single prior art that discloses&#44; either expressly or inherently&#44; each limitation of a claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/08/perricone.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">perricone</span></a>'},{question:"teaching away is irrelevant to anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/seachange-tec-air-haruna-gordon.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">seachange</span></a>'},{question:"Description for the purposes of anticipation can be by drawings alone as well as by words.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/bager.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">bager</span></a>'},{question:"102 prior art proof of efficacy not required for enablement just sufficient for POSITA to carry out invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/novo-impax-hiniker.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">impax</span></a>'},{question:"in order to anticipate prior art must be enabling&#44; but not as to 'use' but only 'suggestions' to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/novo-impax-hiniker.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">novo</span></a>'},{question:"how POSITA understands relative size of a genus or species in particular technology is of critical importance",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/osram.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">OSRAM</span></a>'},{question:"if range covers several compositions&#44; anticipated if one is in prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/cross-nelson-titanium.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">titanium</span></a>'},{question:"102 dispositive ques is wld POSITA reasonably understand/infer from single prior art every claim limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/akamai-giannelli.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">akamai</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation if falls within prior art range; prima facie obvious if overlaps",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/atofina-harris-boesch-peterson.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">atofina&#44; harris&#44; boesch&#44; peterson</span></a>'},{question:"anticipation not an 'ipsissimis verbis' test",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/bond-akzo-standard-havens-festo-omega.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">bond&#44; akzo&#44; standard havens</span></a>'},{question:"to anticipate&#44; prior art need only meet inherently disclosed limitation to extent the patented method does.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/kuhle-king.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">king</span></a>'},{question:"102 prior art are disclosed number of components so great POSITA wouldn't see combination",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/wrigley-kennametal.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">wrigley&#44; kennametal</span></a>'},{question:"The law of anticipation does not require that the reference ‘teach’ what the subject [application] teaches.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/kalman.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">kalman</span></a>'},{question:"well settled that teaching away is irrelevant to anticipation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/leggett.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">leggett</span></a>'},{question:"enablement for prior art to anticipate under 102 does not require utility&#44; unlike under 112.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/impax-gleave-novo.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">impax&#44; gleave&#44; novo</span></a>'},{question:"a 102 if POSITA&#44; reading the ref&#44; would 'at once envisage' claimed arrangement / combination.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/kennametal-petering.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">kennametal&#44; petering</span></a>'},{question:"for 102 description of single embodiment of broadly described subject matter is description of invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/lukach.html"><span style="color: #e69138;">lukach</span></a>'}
     ];
myFlashcards = document.getElementByClass("answer"), i, len = linkArray.length; for (i=0; i<len; i++){ myFlashcards.innerHTML += linkArray[i]; }